comantra.net 2015-09-07

# comantra | comantra india | comantra esolutions | comantra.net

1 . What information do Comantra Agents collect from me?  
2 . When does Comantra collect information from me?  
3 . How is my information used?  
4 . Does Comantra share my personal information with others?  
5 . How does Comantra secure my personal information?  
6 . Does Comantra use cookies to collect information about me?  
7 . What are My Responsibilities in Protecting My Personal Information?  
8 . How can I update my information?  
9 . Does Comantra collect information from children?  
10 . Who can I contact with questions about the security of my information?  
11 . Will this privacy policy change?

.....................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................

What information do Comantra Agents collect from me?

We may collect personal information such as your name, mailing address, phone number, e-mail address, credit card number, and other billing information. 

When does Comantra collect information from me?

When using products or services available from Comantra, you may be asked to provide personal information. For example, you may be asked to provide personal information when you schedule an appointment for services; bring in your product for service; purchase products; contact Comantra call centers; initiate a chat session; with Comantra.

How is my information used?

Comantra uses the information you provide to fulfill requests for service or information; provide customer service; promotions or surveys; offer new products or services; improve the effectiveness of our Web site, marketing endeavors and offers; conduct research and analysis; send marketing communications; or perform other business activities.

Does Comantra share my personal information with others?

Comantra does not sell or rent your personal information to third parties, although we may need to share your personal information with certain third parties such as our service providers and other representatives for limited purposes. For example, Comantra may share personal information with third parties to send marketing communications; service products; conduct research, analysis or administer surveys; send mail and e-mail; process credit card payments, data storage, and hosting services. The third parties with whom Comantra conducts business are only authorized to use your information to perform the service for which they were hired. As part of our agreement with them, they are required to follow the privacy guidelines given to them and to take reasonable measures to ensure your personal information is secure. From time to time, we may be required to share personal information in response to a valid court order, subpoena, government investigation, or as otherwise required by law. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we, in good faith, believe to be unlawful. Comantra may share certain personal information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property, and safety of ourselves and others. Comantra may also transfer personal information in the event of a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, dissolution or similar event.

How does Comantra secure my personal information?

**Security**

Comantra takes reasonable precautions to protect Personal Information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. Comantra's website has safeguards in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the data you provide to us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. In certain areas of Comantra's website, Comantra uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to enhance the security of data transmissions. While Comantra strives to protect your Personal Information, Comantra cannot guarantee the security of the Personal Information, so Comantra urges you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser. Within Comantra, data is stored in controlled servers with limited access by authorized personnel...

**Remote Access**

Comantra Agents use remote access to diagnose and resolve system problems. This lets us access your computer to determine the problem and either repair it or provide advice on possible repair options. By taking advantage of this service, you give permission to a Comantra Agent to log into your computer, which may contain personal information. He or she will only search your computer to determine the cause of the problem and will attempt to minimize interaction with your data. It is your responsibility to ensure that all of your files, especially those containing personal information, are secure to prevent any type of data loss or corruption.

Does Comantra use cookies to collect information about me?

A cookie is a small data file that a Web site or e-mail may send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive. Comantra e-mails and Web sites may use cookies to create a more personalized user experience for visitors. These simulate a continuous connection, letting us remember information about your preferences and session. Comantra uses a third party to place cookies on your computer. Although these may contain a unique user ID, they do not collect or store any identifiable personal information. The Comantra web server automatically collects click stream information such as the address (URL) of the Web site that you came from before visiting COMANTRA.NET, which pages you visit on our site while you’re there, which browser you used to view our site, and any search terms you may have entered, among other things. COMANTRA.NET may also use anonymous click stream data to track which pages visitors view. This helps us understand how visitors use our sites.

1\. Member account, password and security: If any of the Services requires you to open an account, you must complete the registration process by providing us with current, complete and accurate information as prompted by the applicable registration form. You also will choose a password and a user name. You are entirely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and account. Furthermore, you are entirely responsible for any and all activities that occur under your account. You agree to notify Comantra immediately of any unauthorized use of your account or any other breach of security. Comantra will not be liable for any loss that you may incur as a result of someone else using your password or account, either with or without your knowledge. However, you could be held liable for losses incurred by Comantra or another party due to someone else using your account or password. You may not use anyone else's account at any time, without the permission of the account holder. We prefer to keep your personal information accurate and up-to-date. To do this, we provide you with the opportunity to update or modify your personal information including billing and shipping information by logging into your account.  
When you create or change your account, we will send a message to the email address confirming the changes made and options you have chosen. Comantra periodically distributes an e-mail newsletter, and you choose whether you want to receive a newsletter from us when you create your account. If you later decide not to receive the newsletter, you can remove yourself from the mailing list at any time.

2\. Forgotten, Lost or Stolen Information: If you have forgotten your password, we provide a mechanism that e-mails your password to you. Since the "forgot my password" feature sends your password to the email address that you used for registration, do not use an email address that can be accessed by others that you would not want to see or change your Comantra account information.  
Always use caution when giving out any personally identifiable information about yourself or your children in any Communication Services. Comantra does not control or endorse the content, messages or information found in any Communication Services and, therefore, Comantra specifically disclaims any liability with regard to the Communication Services and any actions resulting from your participation in any Communication Services. Managers and hosts are not authorized Comantra spokespersons, and their views do not necessarily reflect those of Comantra.

How can I update my information?

Comantra wants your information and marketing preferences to be complete and accurate. To update your information, call us, send an e-mail to enquiry@comantra.net. If you send an e-mail request please include your current contact information and list the requested changes you would like to have made.

Does Comantra collect information from children?

Comantra will not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information online from children under the age of 13. Comantra is committed to protecting the privacy of children.

Who can I contact with questions about the security of my information?

Please contact our privacy manager to report any known or suspected privacy or security breaches or to submit privacy or security-related questions or complaints. After receiving your inquiry, we will respond within five business days. You may call us , e-mail a request to: info@comantra.net

Will this privacy policy change?

Because Comantra will continue to implement new technologies and improve the services and features provided, this policy is subject to change. If there are changes or additions to this privacy policy, we will post them here or in other formats. If we change our information practices or this privacy policy in such a way that your personal information may be used or shared in a different manner, we will give you the opportunity to opt out of having your information used or shared in that new manner.
